

Duvan José Baena

Medellín, Colombia Carrera 21 Nro. 59 -34 (+57) 3122988419

Professional ID 05255-351402

djbpuerta@hotmail.com

https://duvanbaena.com

### Soft Skills

Agile Methodologies Working Together Lifelong learning

## Certification (8)

Microsoft Certified: Azure Database Administrator

Microsoft Certified: Azure Solutions Architect Expert

Microsoft Certified: DevOps

Engineer Expert

Microsoft Certified: Azure Administrator Associate

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform App Maker

Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals

Microsoft Certified: Azure

Fundamentals

Microsoft Certified: Office 365

Fundamentals

#### About me

I am an English language and literature student; I love read and music, I like software development. I am an open-source believer and a faithful follower of DevOps. I have knowledge and experience in the public cloud Azure and Azure DevOps platform and power platform (office 365). I am also well informed about the definition of IAC, about the use of methods to release applications to customers through automation CI/CD multi-platform.

Finally, I have knowledge some tasks of SysAdmin (write shell scripts, document everything, check component on-premises and basic handling of Linux.

## Experience

# DevOps & Cloud Engineer - Globo Studio of Colombia S.A.S, (2018 – 2021) Present

Administration within the Azure ecosystem, complemented using CI/CD technologies and management of source code repositories.

Monitoring the availability of Cloud PaaS/SaaS solutions, performance, and production of health systems in support of meeting service level objectives.

## IT Infrastructure Engineer - Colombia National Police 2008 - 2018

Research, advise, and implement the best practices to maintain the infrastructure.

Maximizing network efficiency by monitoring performance, troubleshooting network problems and outages, scheduling upgrades.

#### Education

### University of Medellin, Col (2019 - 2020)

Software Engineering Specialist

CESDE, Col (2015 - 2018)

Computer Software Technician

Universidad Católica Luis Amigó, Col (2011 - 2017)

Systems Engineering Degree